webmaster.com 2009-12-17

# WebMaster Incorporated

Privacy Policy | Anti-Spam PolicyThis privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for WebMaster Incorporated as they apply to the [webmaster.com](http://www.webmaster.com/), [conferenceroom.com](http://www.conferenceroom.com/) and [webchat.org](http://www.webchat.org/) domains. 

Our postal address is:  
WebMaster Incorporated  
1601 Civic Center Drive  
Suite 100  
Santa Clara, CA 95050 

We may be reached via e-mail at [info@webmaster.com](mailto:info@webmaster.com)

Third Party Advertisers 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and all other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  

Information Collection and Use 

WebMaster Incorporated is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website. 

Registration 

A user is not required to register to use our web site, certain products do require registration to use. This information may be sent to select advertisers if the user chooses. 

Children Under 13 

In Compliance of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, we will not rent or sell children's personally identifiable information to anyone or contact children under 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes. We do and must, however, act upon subpoenas, court orders or legal process, to the extent permitted by law. 

Cookies 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. At this time, WebMaster Incorporated does not use cookies. 

Our advertisers may use cookies to target their banners, and we have no access to or control over these cookies. 

Log Files 

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

Choice/Opt-out 

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site. Users may choose to stop receiving select mailings at any time. 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an outside party, or not. 

Links 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that WebMaster Incorporated is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

Newsletters 

WebMaster Incorporated will send out occasional Newsletters or offers of products to its mailing lists. Users can remove themselves from receiving this information at any time. 

Surveys & Contests 

From time-to-time our site may request information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

Site and Service Updates 

We send all registered users site and service announcement updates. Members may un-subscribe from these mailings, which contain important information about the service, though it is discouraged. 

Correction/Updating 

Personal Information in a users online profile may be changed at any time. 

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

* * *

Anti-Spam Policy

This anti-spam statement discloses the mailing list and promotional practices for WebMaster Incorporated as they apply to the [webmaster.com](http://www.webmaster.com/) and [conferenceroom.com](http://www.conferenceroom.com/) domains.

Our postal address is:  
WebMaster Incorporated  
1601 Civic Center Drive  
Suite 100  
Santa Clara, CA 95050 

We may be reached via e-mail at [info@webmaster.com](mailto:info@webmaster.com)

Mailing Lists 

We will occasionally send out NewsLetters, Promotional Items, Product Updates and other information to email addresses that have been accumulated from our web site. 

Email Address Accumulation 

Email address are accumulated from user registration, product registration and promotions. WebMaster Incorporated does not purchase or use external mailing lists. 

Opt-Out 

We maintain an opt-out list of email addresses and will compare that list against each mailing that we send out. 

Notices 

All emails that are sent out to our lists will contain our corporate address, phone number and primary email address along with information on how to remove themselves from that list as well as instructions on hot to opt-out of any future mailing list activity. 

Choice/Opt-out 

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for the information. If a user opts to receive information from our sponsors, his or her email address will be leased to 24/7 Media. Users may choose to stop receiving select mailings at any time. To opt-out of any future emailings you can email optout@webmaster.com, or you can send us mail to the address listed above. 

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our anti-spam policy, we will post those changes on this page so our users are always aware of our current policy.
